[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Right, Chunk?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "Chunk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "To her very famous friends.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "her", "very", "famous", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "For what?", "question_tokens": ["For", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Well, you know what.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "what", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "ORGAN: Guilty.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Guilty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Would you have done that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I wouldn't have -- I don't know that I would have bumped you for -- no, I don't bump people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "have", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "I", "would", "have", "bumped", "you", "for", "--", "no", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "bump", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "For President Obama?", "question_tokens": ["For", "President", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "You'd turn down the president for me?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'d", "turn", "down", "the", "president", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, this isn't a real circumstance that you're talking about.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "n't", "a", "real", "circumstance", "that", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "With you?", "question_tokens": ["With", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Where you've been cruelly bounceful (ph).", "answer_tokens": ["Where", "you", "'ve", "been", "cruelly", "bounceful", "(", "ph", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Of Charlie Sheen?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "Charlie", "Sheen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What do you think of the whole crazy Sheen circus?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "whole", "crazy", "Sheen", "circus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "I think it's a pretty bunch of a hot mess.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "pretty", "bunch", "of", "a", "hot", "mess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "ORGAN: You've been of a hot mess?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "You", "'ve", "been", "of", "a", "hot", "mess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "I got here on time, didn't I?", "question_tokens": ["I", "got", "here", "on", "time", ",", "did", "n't", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "You did.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And we just thought, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "we", "just", "thought", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I know it's weird --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "it", "'s", "weird", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Any of that planned for me this evening?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "of", "that", "planned", "for", "me", "this", "evening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "No, I won't touch your genitals.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "wo", "n't", "touch", "your", "genitals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "You haven't read it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "n't", "read", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Well, obviously you grab people's BlackBerries and you just send appalling stuff to all their contacts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", "you", "grab", "people", "'s", "BlackBerries", "and", "you", "just", "send", "appalling", "stuff", "to", "all", "their", "contacts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Is it funny?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "funny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "ANDLER: It is.", "answer_tokens": ["ANDLER", ":", "It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What do you write?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "write", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, like I'll send out, you know, e-mails from people on staff to their friends and family.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "like", "I", "'ll", "send", "out", ",", "you", "know", ",", "e-mails", "from", "people", "on", "staff", "to", "their", "friends", "and", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Has it damaged you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "damaged", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Does it make you seek out an audience, looking for some bit of approval?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "make", "you", "seek", "out", "an", "audience", ",", "looking", "for", "some", "bit", "of", "approval", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "You still do stand-up?", "question_tokens": ["You", "still", "do", "stand-up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Do -- yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Do you remember dying on your back side?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "dying", "on", "your", "back", "side", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "What is that like for a stand-up?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "like", "for", "a", "stand-up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "The worst feeling in the entire universe is to bomb.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "worst", "feeling", "in", "the", "entire", "universe", "is", "to", "bomb", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Could you handle that?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "handle", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Chuy, want to say hi to Norman?", "question_tokens": ["Chuy", ",", "want", "to", "say", "hi", "to", "Norman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Probably not, right?", "question_tokens": ["Probably", "not", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "You look very beautiful.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "look", "very", "beautiful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Well, don't we all, darling?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "n't", "we", "all", ",", "darling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Do you watch your show?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "watch", "your", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Occasionally.", "answer_tokens": ["Occasionally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Why is she so obnoxious?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "she", "so", "obnoxious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Well, she also -- her mother passed away.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "also", "--", "her", "mother", "passed", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Is there a difference between ego and narcissism?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "difference", "between", "ego", "and", "narcissism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What's the difference, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "difference", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, if you're constantly -- you can care what people think about you, but you shouldn't only be serving yourself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "constantly", "--", "you", "can", "care", "what", "people", "think", "about", "you", ",", "but", "you", "should", "n't", "only", "be", "serving", "yourself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Who's going to hire him?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "going", "to", "hire", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, he's a great life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "a", "great", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Life doesn't get much better, does it?", "question_tokens": ["Life", "does", "n't", "get", "much", "better", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RBR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What is the -- I presume I can ask you anything, right?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "--", "I", "presume", "I", "can", "ask", "you", "anything", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "You can.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Much-discussed and speculated on love life?", "question_tokens": ["Much-discussed", "and", "speculated", "on", "love", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Who are you currently having sex with?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "you", "currently", "having", "sex", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I don't -- first of all I have to get his name because -- remind me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "first", "of", "all", "I", "have", "to", "get", "his", "name", "because", "--", "remind", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "It's that good, huh?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "that", "good", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "(INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "That sounds familiar actually.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "sounds", "familiar", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 401, "question": "We all know who I'm dating, what do you want me to talk about?", "question_tokens": ["We", "all", "know", "who", "I", "'m", "dating", ",", "what", "do", "you", "want", "me", "to", "talk", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I'm just surprised --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "surprised", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "His underwear?", "question_tokens": ["His", "underwear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "This woman that tells every shocking detail about her love, sex life and this that, suddenly goes all coy on me.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "woman", "that", "tells", "every", "shocking", "detail", "about", "her", "love", ",", "sex", "life", "and", "this", "that", ",", "suddenly", "goes", "all", "coy", "on", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Do we?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "We do.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "You've learned about privacy, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "learned", "about", "privacy", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, I've learned to respect somebody else's privacy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "learned", "to", "respect", "somebody", "else", "'s", "privacy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Tell me what was the truth of you and old 50?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "what", "was", "the", "truth", "of", "you", "and", "old", "50", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "We dated.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "dated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "And what happened?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Nothing -- you know he's a very sweet and nice guy, but obviously -- I was just sampling, kind of the atmosphere and seeing what was out there.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "--", "you", "know", "he", "'s", "a", "very", "sweet", "and", "nice", "guy", ",", "but", "obviously", "--", "I", "was", "just", "sampling", ",", "kind", "of", "the", "atmosphere", "and", "seeing", "what", "was", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "And what was he like to go out with?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "he", "like", "to", "go", "out", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "He's fun.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "He's not what you imagine him to be, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "not", "what", "you", "imagine", "him", "to", "be", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, I don't really like gifts from rappers in general, since I'm not a hooker, but no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "like", "gifts", "from", "rappers", "in", "general", ",", "since", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "hooker", ",", "but", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Is there a semblance of truth there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "semblance", "of", "truth", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "I've returned gifts, but I've returned gifts to plenty of people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "returned", "gifts", ",", "but", "I", "'ve", "returned", "gifts", "to", "plenty", "of", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "How do you feel about being called the male -- the female version of Ryan Seacrest?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "called", "the", "male", "--", "the", "female", "version", "of", "Ryan", "Seacrest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "He's the female version of Ryan Seacrest.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "the", "female", "version", "of", "Ryan", "Seacrest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Ryan Seacrest?", "question_tokens": ["Ryan", "Seacrest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "What has happened with your contract?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "happened", "with", "your", "contract", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Well, it expires soon.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "expires", "soon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "No, that's how much it costs to rent me for the night.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "how", "much", "it", "costs", "to", "rent", "me", "for", "the", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Well, what are you worth?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "are", "you", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "What is -- I am ruthless when it comes to business, but was it your worth?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "--", "I", "am", "ruthless", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "business", ",", "but", "was", "it", "your", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Well, then you know what you're worth.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "then", "you", "know", "what", "you", "'re", "worth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How?", "question_tokens": ["How", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "ANDLER: Why are you -- shut up.", "answer_tokens": ["ANDLER", ":", "Why", "are", "you", "--", "shut", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Why are you being so coy again?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "being", "so", "coy", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Because it's gross.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "gross", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "How would you like to spend this money you don't want to talk about?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "spend", "this", "money", "you", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I like vacations a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "vacations", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Are you generous?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "generous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yes, I'm very generous.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "very", "generous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "What's the worst?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "worst", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I have no patience.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "patience", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Does that make you naturally mischievous bordering on annoying?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "make", "you", "naturally", "mischievous", "bordering", "on", "annoying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "I've crossed the line into annoying several times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "crossed", "the", "line", "into", "annoying", "several", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Did you hear when I just said?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "hear", "when", "I", "just", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Vodka?", "question_tokens": ["Vodka", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Are you just a compulsive liar?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "just", "a", "compulsive", "liar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Wait.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "What are kind of girl are you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "kind", "of", "girl", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I'm -- you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "I want to hear it from your lips?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "hear", "it", "from", "your", "lips", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I'm a pain in the ass.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "pain", "in", "the", "ass", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "But in quite a good way?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "quite", "a", "good", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "I think it's OK.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "With who?", "question_tokens": ["With", "who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Two of the guys -- both of the people I dated.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "of", "the", "guys", "--", "both", "of", "the", "people", "I", "dated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Is one the current one?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "one", "the", "current", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Maybe.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Not yet?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Who was the other one?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "was", "the", "other", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "My ex-boyfriend Ted.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "ex-boyfriend", "Ted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Is he?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Will you tell him hello for me?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "tell", "him", "hello", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Yes, I will.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Anything you want to say?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "you", "want", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Do you think I mince my words?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "I", "mince", "my", "words", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Is it wise to dip your pen in company ink?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "wise", "to", "dip", "your", "pen", "in", "company", "ink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "I don't think it really matters.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "really", "matters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Because it's fun and it gives us something to watch.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "fun", "and", "it", "gives", "us", "something", "to", "watch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "How have you resisted getting married?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "resisted", "getting", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Well, that's an interesting question as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "interesting", "question", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "But do you have a little part of you that dreams wistfully of a fairy tale wedding?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "have", "a", "little", "part", "of", "you", "that", "dreams", "wistfully", "of", "a", "fairy", "tale", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I wouldn't say that, no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "say", "that", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Can you believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "That's what I'm getting at.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "I", "'m", "getting", "at", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "What marriage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Are you having twins?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "having", "twins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "You're not pregnant?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "pregnant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "No, not that I know of.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "that", "I", "know", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Would you like children?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "Never going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "I hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Because I'm not somebody that wants to be a mother.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "not", "somebody", "that", "wants", "to", "be", "a", "mother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Because I think you would be a good mother.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "think", "you", "would", "be", "a", "good", "mother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Like a little Chelsea to play with?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "a", "little", "Chelsea", "to", "play", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chelsea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Really makes you laugh?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "makes", "you", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "I guess everyone that I work with.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "everyone", "that", "I", "work", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "What was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "I think both.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 825, "question": "What's the worst type of guest for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "worst", "type", "of", "guest", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "People who are so nervous.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "who", "are", "so", "nervous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 834, "question": "If you were doing a more serious thing, what kind of issues really get you going?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "doing", "a", "more", "serious", "thing", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "issues", "really", "get", "you", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 835, "answer": "Well, I'm interested in politics.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "interested", "in", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "Any politicians that you just can't stand?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "politicians", "that", "you", "just", "ca", "n't", "stand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "ANDLER: Well, Boehner is ridiculous.", "answer_tokens": ["ANDLER", ":", "Well", ",", "Boehner", "is", "ridiculous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "Are you a fan of hers?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "fan", "of", "hers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "That's not a serious person.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "a", "serious", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 857, "question": "President Trump?", "question_tokens": ["President", "Trump", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 858, "answer": "That's getting interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "getting", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS"], "qSentId": 860, "question": "Is he?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "He is way ahead in all the polls", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "way", "ahead", "in", "all", "the", "polls"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "What else do we have to go on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "do", "we", "have", "to", "go", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "Well, hopefully our minds, because that would be ridiculous if Donald Trump became president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "hopefully", "our", "minds", ",", "because", "that", "would", "be", "ridiculous", "if", "Donald", "Trump", "became", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Would it be ridiculous?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "be", "ridiculous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "Yes, it would.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 871, "question": "Was that really his fault?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "really", "his", "fault", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 872, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 873, "question": "Do you think so?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 874, "answer": "Well, not entirely.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "entirely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "Would anybody have been governor of California in that financial crisis and not caught a big cold?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "anybody", "have", "been", "governor", "of", "California", "in", "that", "financial", "crisis", "and", "not", "caught", "a", "big", "cold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "No, I think he was very irresponsible.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "he", "was", "very", "irresponsible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "Did you vote for Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "vote", "for", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 887, "question": "Would you again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 888, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ":", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "Well, I think it takes a long time to get things accomplished?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "takes", "a", "long", "time", "to", "get", "things", "accomplished", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "That wasn't really -- that wasn't the question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "n't", "really", "--", "that", "was", "n't", "the", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 905, "question": "Have you met him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 906, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "He asked me where Chewy was actually.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "asked", "me", "where", "Chewy", "was", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "He didn't?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "He did.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 922, "question": "What does the future hold for Chelsea Handler Incorporated, this burgeoning empire?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "the", "future", "hold", "for", "Chelsea", "Handler", "Incorporated", ",", "this", "burgeoning", "empire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 923, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chelsea Handler Incorporated"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 939, "question": "What kind of question is that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "question", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 940, "answer": "You don't have to be so touchy about it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "be", "so", "touchy", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 944, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 945, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 946, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 947, "answer": "I'm just talking about my feelings.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "talking", "about", "my", "feelings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 950, "question": "Where does this empire go next?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "this", "empire", "go", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 951, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 955, "question": "Do you want to stay there?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "stay", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 956, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 963, "question": "Choose any job in the world?", "question_tokens": ["Choose", "any", "job", "in", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 964, "answer": "ANDLER: I'm producing a bunch of TV shows.", "answer_tokens": ["ANDLER", ":", "I", "'m", "producing", "a", "bunch", "of", "TV", "shows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", ":", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 969, "question": "What's been the most ridiculous thing you read about yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "most", "ridiculous", "thing", "you", "read", "about", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 970, "answer": "Oh -- I mean -- well, the easiest thing that people -- people can write about me, because I'm so forthcoming about my life and that I like Belvedere, you know, and that I'm not a stickler for a lot of rules in my personal life or that kind of thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "--", "I", "mean", "--", "well", ",", "the", "easiest", "thing", "that", "people", "--", "people", "can", "write", "about", "me", ",", "because", "I", "'m", "so", "forthcoming", "about", "my", "life", "and", "that", "I", "like", "Belvedere", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "that", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "stickler", "for", "a", "lot", "of", "rules", "in", "my", "personal", "life", "or", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 978, "question": "Ever do that?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 979, "answer": "We don't -- no, we don't.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "--", "no", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 981, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 982, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 997, "question": "What do you do when you go out together?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "when", "you", "go", "out", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 998, "answer": "ANDLER: We go over to her house, hang out.", "answer_tokens": ["ANDLER", ":", "We", "go", "over", "to", "her", "house", ",", "hang", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 1010, "question": "She wouldn't be real?", "question_tokens": ["She", "would", "n't", "be", "real", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1011, "answer": "You could have a conversation with her.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "could", "have", "a", "conversation", "with", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP$", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1015, "question": "If you could relive one moment in your life in five minutes to live, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "relive", "one", "moment", "in", "your", "life", "in", "five", "minutes", "to", "live", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1016, "answer": "I would say the best moment of my life would be when my \"Chelsea Chelsea Bang Bang\" book came out last year, and they called to tell me that I was number one on the list --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "the", "best", "moment", "of", "my", "life", "would", "be", "when", "my", "``", "Chelsea", "Chelsea", "Bang", "Bang", "''", "book", "came", "out", "last", "year", ",", "and", "they", "called", "to", "tell", "me", "that", "I", "was", "number", "one", "on", "the", "list", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "JJS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 1017, "question": "On \"the New York Times\" best seller?", "question_tokens": ["On", "``", "the", "New", "York", "Times", "''", "best", "seller", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1018, "answer": "On \"the New York Times\" best seller, but my other two books were number two and three.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "``", "the", "New", "York", "Times", "''", "best", "seller", ",", "but", "my", "other", "two", "books", "were", "number", "two", "and", "three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1029, "question": "Why would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1030, "answer": "Because I have no business writing books.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "have", "no", "business", "writing", "books", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1045, "question": "Do you both 100 percent believe she's still alive or do you have to believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "both", "100", "percent", "believe", "she", "'s", "still", "alive", "or", "do", "you", "have", "to", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1046, "answer": "I don't think that we can say 100 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "we", "can", "say", "100", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}]